playnwin.tv 2016-03-10

# Privacy Policy « Play 'n' Win

## Your Details

We may use your Personal Information to tailor your experience on our Services, serve advertising we think may be relevant to you, understand your preferences, and provide you with offers we think may be of interest. It is your responsibility to give us current, complete, truthful and accurate information and to keep the Personal Information you provide us up to date. We are not liable in any way or responsible for damage that may arise if you do not give us accurate, truthful or complete information or you fail to update the information you give us.

We reserve the right to share your Personal Information with subsidiary and affiliated companies, as well as our operational service providers that assist in providing our Service. We will not share Personal Information we obtain solely in connection with our Service with any non-affiliated parties unless you opt in or consent (which you may be doing when you sign up, enroll or participate in any promotion or activity) and you always have the right to opt out at any time. Some aggregate, non-personally identifiable data we collect in connection with our Service may be shared with our advertisers and other business partners, but we do not give any Personal Information to them unless stated in this Privacy Policy or otherwise disclosed to you. Promotions and Advertising  
We may post notices, offers, advertising and promotional material on our Service and we may use your Personal Information to contact you.

By subscribing to Play’n’Win you agree to receive marketing messages via email and SMS. We will only send you details of related products which we believe will be of interest to you. We will send you a maximum of 5 communications a month.

We may make advertisements, promotions and offers from other third parties available through our Service from time to time. You acknowledge and agree that if you respond, take advantage of, accept or register for any offer, enter or provide information to a third party you are deemed to have opted into sharing that information (including Personal Information) with those third parties, you are also acknowledging and agreeing that their privacy policies and terms and conditions (not ours) apply to your relationship with them. We have no control over and no liability or responsibility for these third parties and in no way recommend their services.

## Opt Out Procedures

You may chose to opt out of receiving marketing and promotional e-mails, text or other electronic messages from us by either (i) sending an SMS to our short number, 60699(or other number we designate on our Website), (ii) calling our customer service representatives at 01223590548 or (iii) sending us an e-mail to [cs@zamano.com](mailto:cs@zamano.com). We may always contact you via e-mail or SMS for administrative or informational purposes, including follow-up messages regarding the administration of your subscription, any promotions you have entered or participated in, offers you have accepted or Services you have enrolled in or ordered or any of your transactions related to our Service.  

## Minors

If we unknowingly send an e-mail or SMS text message to anyone under the age of 13 or who has registered in violation of these terms, that individual’s parent always has the right to unsubscribe or direct us to opt out that individual from receiving future e-mails, SMS text messages, text alerts or e-newsletters or request termination of any registration, subscription or use of our Service.
